Preliminary Guide to the Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art, 1960s-2000s SPEC.CGA.JGS
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art
1960s-2000s
SPEC.CGA.JGS
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
31.2 Cubic feet 26 boxes
The collection contains 26 boxes of files created by Joe Szabo in the production of "Witty World" magazine and other publications related to cartoon art.
(26) 12" x 15" x 10" record storage cartons
Arrangement of Materials
The Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art has been preliminary arranged and minimally processed and described, mostly at the box level. Files are alphabetical by artist's last name or by geographic location.
Acquisitions Information
CGA.2017.072: John A. Lent, 2017
Separated Materials
Original art has been separated out and will be cataloged in the Original Art Database. Please check the Original Art Database for updates. Uncataloged original art from this collection is available to researchers, please contact the reading room at cartoons@osu.edu or call 614-292-0538.
Books and other published materials have also been separated out. It will be cataloged in the Ohio State Libraries Catalog under the collection ns2:title "Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art." Please check the catalog for additions.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains files created by Joe Szabo in the production of "Witty World" magazine and other publications related to cartoon art. It has been minimally processed at the box level and preliminarly arranged alaphatically by artists' last name, subject matter, and geographic location. The folder titles were named by Szabo.
Biographical Note
Joseph George Szabo, born February 4, 1950 in Budapest, Hungary. He graduated from the Academy of Journalism in 1974. In 1980, he and his wife emigrated to the United States to escape Communism in Hungary. They settled in North Wales, PA. Joe worked as a freelance cartoonist for a time. In 1987, he found the magazine "Witty World" which chronicled cartooning from around the world. Szabo also launched a variety of print and electronic publications related to cartoon art. He passed away on February 2, 2016 at his home in North Wales, PA.
Related Materials
Works by Joe Szaboi have been cataloged in The Ohio State University Libraries catalog under "Szabo, Joseph, George." Miscellaneous clippings about Dedini may be found in the library's biography file under his last name.
Access to Materials
Materials in this collection are available for use, but may be used in the Billy Ireland Cartoon Library & Museum reading room only. Audio/visual materials and computer media may need a use copy produced before access is allowed. To request materials in the finding aid, please contact cartoons@osu.edu or call the reading room at 614-292-0538
Comic books, strips, etc
- Abdelke, Youssef, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 1)
- Abejide, Sanmi, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 2)
- Abitabile, Paul R., 1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 3)
- Abraham, Daniel, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 4)
- Abrahamian, Emil, 1982-1991 (Box JGS 1, Folder 5)
- Abrahamian, Levon, 1994 (Box JGS 1, Folder 6)
- Abrodmann, 1987-1988 (Box JGS 1, Folder 7)
- Adamowicz, Andrzej, 1986 (Box JGS 1, Folder 8)
- Adams, Scott, 1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 9)
- Adcock, Thomas (Addy), 1954-1988; 1960-2000 (Box JGS 1, Folder 10)
- Adkoli, V.R., undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 11)
- Adolfo, Gustavo, 1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 12)
- Africa, Eli, 1987 (Box JGS 1, Folder 13)
- Agudelo, Jose (Azeta), undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 14)
- Aguila, Dani, 1969-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 15)
- Ainapore, Yasmin, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 16)
- Ainutdinov, Sergei, circa 1992 (Box JGS 1, Folder 17)
- Aislin, 1989 (Box JGS 1, Folder 18)
- Ajanovic, Midhat, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 19)
- Ajauskas, V., circa 1990 (Box JGS 1, Folder 20)
- Ajin, 1983-1987 (Box JGS 1, Folder 21)
- Akgul, Tayfun, 1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 22)
- Akgun, Mahmut, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 23)
- Akhavien, Homan, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 24)
- Akyol, Ercan, 1994 (Box JGS 1, Folder 25)
- Al-Ali, Naji Salim, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 26)
- Al-Awadi, Abdul Wahab, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 27)
- Al-Baghdadi, Abbass, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 28)
- Alcala, Alfredo, 1987 (Box JGS 1, Folder 29)
- Aleman, Carlos Villar, 1992 (Box JGS 1, Folder 30)
- Alexander, Frank, 1955-1971 (Box JGS 1, Folder 31)
- Alexandrescu, A.S., 1990 (Box JGS 1, Folder 32)
- Alfio, Leotta, 1992 (Box JGS 1, Folder 33)
- Al-Garhi, Dr. Saber I., 1991-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 34)
- Alguien, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 35)
- Alimov, Murat, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 1, Folder 36)
- Alizadeh, Javad, 1985-1997 (Box JGS 21, Folder 43, Box JGS 1, Folder 37)
- Allen, Jim, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 38)
- Almond, Art, 1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 39)
- Alvine, Ken, 1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 40)
- Ambrasas, Alvydas, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 41)
- Ameri, Amir Teymour, 1991-1994 (Box JGS 1, Folder 42)
- Ammer, Wolfgang, 1990-1997 (Box JGS 21, Folder 44)
- Amorim, C.A. da Costa, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 43)
- Anderson, Andy, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 44)
- Anderson, Brad, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 45)
- Anderson, David, 1989-1994 (Box JGS 1, Folder 46)
- Anderson, Richard, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 47)
- Andreassen, Arvid, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 48)
- Andronic, Adrian, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 49)
- Angelkoski, N., 1994-1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 50)
- Anjomrouz, S., 1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 51)
- Annestay, Jean, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 52)
- Antonio, 1990-1997 (Box JGS 21, Folder 45)
- Anonimo, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 53)
- Ansul, Steve, 1983-1990 (Box JGS 1, Folder 54)
- Antunes, Antonio, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 55)
- Apfel, Gershon, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 56)
- Aragones, Sergio, 1991 (Box JGS 1, Folder 57)
- Aral, Tekin, 1999 (Box JGS 1, Folder 58)
- Arambula, Roman, 1989 (Box JGS 1, Folder 59)
- Arbach, Jorge, 1990 (Box JGS 1, Folder 60)
- Arbesu, Faustino, 1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 46)
- Arbiza, Conrado, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 61)
- Archelaos, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 62)
- Ares, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 63)
- Armstrong, Rob, 2002 (Box JGS 1, Folder 64)
- Armstrong, Mark, 1990 (Box JGS 1, Folder 65)
- Armstrong, Robb, 1989-1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 66)
- Arroyo, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 67)
- Artley, Steve, 1992 (Box JGS 1, Folder 68)
- Aryanto, 1972 (Box JGS 1, Folder 69)
- Asay, Chuck, 1990 (Box JGS 1, Folder 70)
- Asenjo, Luis Osses, 1954-1997 (Box JGS 21, Folder 47, Box JGS 1, Folder 71)
- Ashraf, Kazi Khaleed, 1992 (Box JGS 1, Folder 72)
- Astalos, I., undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 73)
- Atchison, Michael, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 74)
- Auth, Tony, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 75)
- Aydinlik, Semiramis, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 76)
- Ayrancioglu, A., undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 77)
- Ayres, Erico J., 1991-1992 (Box JGS 1, Folder 78)
- Azar, Joe, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 79)
- Azimov, Ildoos, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 80)
- Baaske, Wolfgang, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 81)
- Babu, Sayadev, 1992 (Box JGS 1, Folder 82)
- Badeaux, Guy, 1985-1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 48)
- Badrudin, Ramli, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 83, Box JGS 21, Folder 49)
- Baghdadi, Abbass, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 84)
- Bagnall, Brian, 1980-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 85)
- Bahgory, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 1, Folder 86)
- Bahrainian, Amir, 1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 87)
- Bai, Weichun, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 88)
- Baker, Aladin Saad Abu, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 89)
- Bakke, Dagfinn, 1984-1996 (Box JGS 1, Folder 90, Box JGS 21, Folder 50)
- Bakova, B., 1990 (Box JGS 1, Folder 91)
- Bakowski, Grzegorz, undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 92)
- Balgar, Vladimir, 1965-1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 93)
- Baldasaro, B., undated (Box JGS 1, Folder 94)
- Baldwin, Wayne, 1986-1989 (Box JGS 1, Folder 95)
- Ballantine, 1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 51)
- Balogh, L., 1991-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 96)
- Banegas, 1992-1997 (Box JGS 21, Folder 52, Box JGS 1, Folder 97)
- Barbara, E.C., 1993 (Box JGS 1, Folder 98)
- Barbour, David, 1989 (Box JGS 1, Folder 99)
- Barbu, Ion, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 1, Folder 100)
- Barecki, Andrzej, 1983-1989 (Box JGS 1, Folder 101)
- Barker, James, 1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 1)
- Barnhart, Duane, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 2)
- Barrett, Hope, 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 3)
- Barst, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 4)
- Bartak, Miroslav, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 5)
- Bartfeld, A., 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 6)
- Barton, Les, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 7)
- Barvircak, Miroslav, 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 8)
- Basset, Gene, 1985-1987 (Box JGS 2, Folder 9)
- Bastos, Rafael, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 10)
- Basyrov, Garif, 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 11)
- Batai, Sandor, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 12)
- Batca, Mircea, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 13)
- Bates, Bill, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 14)
- Batten, Theo, 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 15)
- Baudelet, Roland, 1988 (Box JGS 2, Folder 16)
- Baures, Robert, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 2, Folder 17)
- Bauer, Gerd, 1983-1986 (Box JGS 2, Folder 18)
- Bave, Terry, 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 19)
- Bayanzul, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 20)
- Baysal, Ercan, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 21)
- Beattie, Bruce, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 22)
- Beck, C.C., undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 23)
- Beck, Chip, 1989-1991 (Box JGS, Folder 24)
- Beckett, Samuel, 1986 (Box JGS 2, Folder 25)
- Beers, Scooter, 1989-1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 26)
- Behrendt, Fritz, 1990-1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 27)
- Beier, Roland, 1988-1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 28)
- Bekesi, Josef S., 1990-1996 (Box JGS 2, Folder 29, Box JGS 21, Folder 53)
- Belhomme, JeanLoic, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 30)
- Belin, Nat, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 31)
- Bell, Steve, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 32)
- Belortaja, Medi, circa 1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 33)
- Bender, Gregg, 1990 (Box JGS 2, Folder 34)
- Benitez, Jerez, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 35)
- Benito, Oscar T.F. (Beno), 1991-1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 36)
- Benson, Steve, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 37)
- Bentley, Kenneth, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 38)
- Bentley, Stephen, 1989-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 39)
- Ben-Uri, Boaz, circa 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 40)
- Bercea, Radu, 1990 (Box JGS 2, Folder 41)
- Berenson, David, 1997 (Box JGS 2, Folder 42)
- Beresniovas, Vladimiras, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 43)
- Berg, Olle, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 44)
- Berg, Olof, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 45)
- Berman, Jennifer, 1988-1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 46)
- Berry, Abe, 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 47)
- Berry, Jim, 1986-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 48)
- Bernazzali, Nino, 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 49)
- Berryman, Chris, 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 50)
- Best, Paul, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 51)
- Best, Steve, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 52)
- Beutel, Josh, 1990-1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 53)
- Bevington, Geoff, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 54)
- Bey, 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 55)
- Bianes, John G., 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 56)
- Bibishev, V., 1993-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 57)
- Bidstrup, Herluf, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 58)
- Bier, Augusto, 1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 59)
- Bin, Chen Shu, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 60)
- Binakhani, Asad A., undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 61)
- Biret, Ismail, 1993-1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 62)
- Black, Robert A., 1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 63)
- Blain, S., undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 64)
- Blecha, Josef, 1979-1988 (Box JGS 2, Folder 65)
- Block, Herbert, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 2, Folder 66)
- Bloom, Neal, circa 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 67)
- Blumenkrantz, Gerardo, 1989-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 68)
- Bobylev, Sergei, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 69)
- Bobir, Alexandr, 1988 (Box JGS 2, Folder 70)
- Bobun, Alexander, 1988 (Box JGS 2, Folder 71)
- Bogan, Paulette, 1988 (Box JGS 2, Folder 72)
- Bogorad, Victor, 1994-1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 54, Box JGS 2, Folder 73)
- Bohme, Ralf, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 74)
- Boileau, Linda, 1985-1987 (Box JGS 2, Folder 75)
- Bolduc, Sylvain, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 2, Folder 76)
- Bonehill, Jos., undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 77)
- Booch, Ramesh S., 1986-1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 78)
- Booth, 1986 (Box JGS 2, Folder 79)
- Boren, Jim, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 80)
- Borer, Johannes, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 2, Folder 81)
- Borgman, Jim, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 2, Folder 82)
- Borisic, V., 1991-1996 (Box JGS 2, Folder 83)
- Born, Adolf, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 84)
- Boro, Len, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 85)
- Boros, Stefan, Olimp Boros (Tety), undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 86)
- Bortolotti, Aldo, 1992-1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 87)
- Bosnic, Dragan, 1983-1986 (Box JGS 2, Folder 88)
- Bosschaert, Jan, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 89)
- Botella, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 90)
- Botezatu, Pavel, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 91)
- Bottorff, William, 1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 92)
- Bousquet, Don, 1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 93)
- Boutet, Francois, 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 94)
- Bouthillier, Art, 1988 (Box JGS 2, Folder 95)
- Bozinouska, S., undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 96)
- Bohme, Ralf, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 97)
- (Brasser) Pol de Valck, circa 1992 (Box JGS 2, Folder 98)
- Breathed, Berke, 1983-1989 (Box JGS 2, Folder 99)
- Breccia, Alberto, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 100)
- Breisacher, George, 1996 (Box JGS 2, Folder 101)
- Brenner, George, 1989 (Box JGS 2, Folder 102)
- Brkic, Frank, 1996-1997 (Box JGS 2, Folder 103)
- Brock, 1995 (Box JGS 2, Folder 104)
- Brodman, Alfred, 1987 (Box JGS 2, Folder 105)
- Brogan, Madeleine, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 106)
- Bromhead, 1988 (Box JGS 2, Folder 107)
- Bronski, Z., 1993-1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 108)
- Bronzit, Konstantin, 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 109)
- Broto, Kuncoro, 1996 (Box JGS 2, Folder 110)
- Brown, Roger, 1989 (Box JGS 2, Folder 111)
- Browne, Dik, Chris Browne, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 2, Folder 112)
- Brunelle, Albert, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 113)
- Brynjolfsson, S.O., undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 114)
- Bubec, undated (Box JGS 2, Folder 115)
- Buchanan, Cole, 1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 116)
- Buckley, Desmond, 1987-1993 (Box JGS 2, Folder 117)
- Buckley, Jerry, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 118)
- Budak, Asaf, 1991 (Box JGS 2, Folder 119)
- Buford, Mark, 1997 (Box JGS 3, Folder 1)
- Buglioni, Pier Luigi, 1973-1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 2)
- Buhajeruk, J.C., 1994 (Box JGS 2, Folder 3)
- Bukovac, Milan, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 4)
- Bulatov, Ali, 1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 5)
- Bunikis, A., 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 6)
- Burg, Ben, 1994 (Box JGS 3, Folder 7)
- Burkamp, Dieter, 1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 55)
- Burneckis, S., undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 8)
- Burton, Martin, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 9)
- Bushmiller, Ernie, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 9)
- Button, Ford, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 10)
- Buttrum, P.D., 1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 11)
- Bynoe, Julian J., undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 12)
- Cabanas, Jose Luis, 1985 (Box JGS 3, Folder 13)
- Cagle, Daryl, 1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 14)
- Cajas, 1991 (Box JGS 3, Folder 15)
- Caldari, Eduardo, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 16)
- Cajchan, Juraj, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 17)
- Cakmak, Huseyin, 1995-1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 18)
- Caldari, Eduardo, 1992-1998 (Box JGS 3, Folder 19)
- Calvo, Roy Solis, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 20)
- Campaner, Angelo, 1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 21)
- Caniff, Milton, 1987 (Box JGS 3, Folder 22)
- Canning, Eileen, 1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 23)
- Capp, Al, 1948-1988 (Box JGS 3, Folder 24)
- Cardio, Horacio, 1988 (Box JGS 3, Folder 25)
- Carlson, Lee, 1976-1997 (Box JGS 3, Folder 26)
- Carlson, Stuart, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 27)
- Carlucho, 1990-1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 28)
- Cartin, Victor (Tin Glao), 1985-1992 (Box JGS 3, Folder 29)
- de Carvalho, Al N., 1999 (Box JGS 3, Folder 30)
- Carvalho, M.A. (Michelangelo), undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 31)
- Caceres, German, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 78)
- Cakmak, Huseyin, 1988-1996 (Box JGS 19, Folder 79)
- Casey, Liza, 1988 (Box JGS 3, Folder 32)
- Cassani, Ruben, 1997 (Box JGS 3, Folder 33)
- Cassady, John, 1985-1997 (Box JGS 3, Folder 34)
- Castiblanco (Fernandez), undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 35)
- Castillejos, Serge (Cas), 1988 (Box JGS 3, Folder 36)
- Caudill, Arthur, 1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 37)
- Cavallerin, Sergio, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 38)
- Cavallo, Giorgio, 1994 (Box JGS 3, Folder 39)
- Cavey, Robert, 1988 (Box JGS 3, Folder 40)
- Cavna, Mike, 1997 (Box JGS 3, Folder 41)
- Cebula, Henryk, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 42)
- Cecil, Charles A., 1989-1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 43)
- Cecilcanin, Goran, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 44)
- Celikkol, Ali Herkul, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 45)
- Chadburn, Steve, 1992-1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 46)
- Chandran, 1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 47)
- Chao, Johnny, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 48)
- Chacon, Ross, 1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 49)
- Chard, 1978-1987 (Box JGS 3, Folder 50)
- Cheah, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 51)
- Chegodayev, G., 1991 (Box JGS 3, Folder 52)
- Cheng, Qu Chuan, 1994 (Box JGS 3, Folder 53)
- Cheng, Fang, 1985-1996 (Box JGS 15, Folder 57, Box JGS 3, Folder 54)
- Chernyshev, N., undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 55)
- Chin, Tsai Hai, 1989 (Box JGS 3, Folder 56)
- Ching-Jung, Law, 1976-1986 (Box JGS 3, Folder 57)
- Chip, Bok, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 58)
- Chiuz, Sergio, 1990-1992 (Box JGS 3, Folder 59)
- Chodorowski, Antoni, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 60-61)
- Chow, Ming Fai, 1991 (Box JGS 3, Folder 62)
- Chu, Ronald, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 63)
- Ciosu, Constantin, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 64)
- Cizmazia, K., 1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 65)
- Clark, Gary, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 66)
- Clark, John, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 67)
- Clark, Lawrence, 1992 (Box JGS 3, Folder 68)
- Clement, Pierre (Kapoun), undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 69)
- Cleveland, Michael, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 70)
- Coching, Fracisco, 1987 (Box JGS 3, Folder 71)
- Coco (J.L.Z. Magano), 1990-1992 (Box JGS 3, Folder 72)
- Coguplugil, Orhan, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 73)
- Cohen, Mark J., 1990-1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 74)
- Coker, Paul, 1989 (Box JGS 3, Folder 75)
- Collart, Gerard, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 76)
- Colley, Ed, 1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 77)
- Collins, Betty, 1987 (Box JGS 3, Folder 78)
- Collins, Clive, 1990-1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 79)
- Collins, David, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 80)
- Colt, David, 1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 81)
- Conrad, Paul, 1987-1992 (Box JGS 3, Folder 82)
- Constantin, Pavel, 1989-1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 83, Box JGS 19, Folder 80)
- Contemori, Lido, 1994 (Box JGS 3, Folder 84)
- Copeland, John, 1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 85)
- Corax (Koraksic, Predrag), 1988-1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 86)
- Corio, Paul, 1988 (Box JGS 3, Folder 87)
- Cork, 1992 (Box JGS 3, Folder 88)
- Cosenza, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 89)
- Coutarelli, 1993-1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 90)
- Coverly, Dave, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 91)
- Covo, Javier, 1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 92)
- Craig, David, 1989 (Box JGS 3, Folder 93)
- Crane, Roy, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 94)
- Cravens, Greg, undated (Box JGS 3, Folder 95)
- Crenshaw, George, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 3, Folder 96)
- Crihana, Florian-Doru, 1988-1994 (Box JGS 3, Folder 97)
- Crivelli, 1986 (Box JGS 3, Folder 98)
- Crocker, Jim, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 99)
- Cruikshank, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 100)
- Crumb, Robert, 1990 (Box JGS 3, Folder 101)
- Cruse, Howard, 1987 (Box JGS 3, Folder 102)
- Cruz, Julia, 1986 (Box JGS 3, Folder 103)
- Csaszar, Tamas, 1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 104)
- Cudo, Dimitar, 1987-1991 (Box JGS 3, Folder 105)
- Cummings, Dale, 1993 (Box JGS 3, Folder 106)
- Curtis, Chris, 1991-1996 (Box JGS 3, Folder 107)
- Curtis, Thomas P., 1991 (Box JGS 3, Folder 108)
- Curtu, Valeriu, 1984-1992 (Box JGS 3, Folder 109)
- Cusimano, Mick, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 3, Folder 110)
- Czeczot, Andrzej, 1980 (Box JGS 3, Folder 111)
- Czura, Victor, 1986 (Box JGS 3, Folder 112)
- Dahm, Bob, 1988 (Box JGS 4, Folder 1)
- Dale, Barbara and Jim, 1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 2)
- Dale, Terry, 1988 (Box JGS 4, Folder 3)
- Dallimore, P., undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 4)
- Dallos, Jeno, 1984-1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 5)
- Dalvand, Ahmad, 1986-1987 (Box JGS 4, Folder 6)
- Danesh, Parvish, 1988-1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 7)
- Danyal, Nezih, 1999 (Box JGS 4, Folder 8)
- Danziger, Jeff, 1994 (Box JGS 4, Folder 9)
- Dar, Sudhir, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 10)
- Darroch, Bob, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 4, Folder 11)
- Daskalov, T.G., undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 12)
- David, Mark, 1987 (Box JGS 4, Folder 13)
- David, Werner, 1987 (Box JGS 4, Folder 14)
- Davidson, John, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 15)
- Davis, Jack, 1976 (Box JGS 4, Folder 16)
- Davis, Ken, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 17)
- Davis, Jim, 1978-1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 18)
- Day, Bill, 1994-1998 (Box JGS 4, Folder 19)
- Dazeley, G, 1999 (Box JGS 4, Folder 20)
- Dreamicis, John, 1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 21)
- Dean, S. Percy, 1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 22)
- de Angelis, Marco, 1988-1997 (Box JGS 4, Folder 23, Box JGS 19, Folder 81)
- de Borger, Leon (Lejon), 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 24)
- Dedini, Eldon, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 25)
- de Fazio, Gary, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 26)
- Degenfeld-Schonburg, Paul, 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 27)
- Degtyarev, Alexey, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 28)
- Dergatchov, Oleg, 1993-1995 (Box JGS 4, Folder 29)
- De Roo, Marc, 1985 (Box JGS 4, Folder 30)
- de Salles, Jorge, circa 1977 (Box JGS 4, Folder 31)
- Delambre, 1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 32)
- Delatiri, Anthony, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 33)
- Delgado, Roy, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 34)
- Delmonte, Steve, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 35)
- Demir, Oguz, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 36)
- de Moya, Alvaro, 1990-1997 (Box JGS 19, Folder 82)
- Dempsey, John, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 37)
- Denevert, 1988 (Box JGS 4, Folder 38)
- Deore, Bill, 1990 (Box JGS 4, Folder 39)
- Derambakhsh, Kambiz, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 4, Folder 40)
- Despodoff, Boris, 1990 (Box JGS 4, Folder 41)
- Desseyn, Johan, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 42)
- Dias, Ronaldo C., 1987-1995 (Box JGS 4, Folder 43)
- Diaz, 1983 (Box JGS 4, Folder 44)
- Dierick, Hans, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 45)
- Diker, Erdogan, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 46)
- Dimitrov, Dimitar (Dim), undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 47)
- Dincay, U.M., 1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 49)
- Dinardo, Bill, 1986 (Box JGS 4, Folder 48)
- Divandari, A., 1990-1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 50)
- Laszlo, Dluhopolszky, 1984-1998 (Box JGS 4, Folder 51, Box JGS 19, Folder 83)
- Dochev, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 52)
- Dodal, J., undated (Box JGS, Folder 53)
- Dodd, Ed, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 54)
- Dodds, Glenn, 1985-1986 (Box JGS 4, Folder 55)
- Dodsworth, Peter, 1990 (Box JGS 4, Folder 56)
- Dogu, Orhan, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 57)
- Donarelli, Franco, 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 58)
- Dorf, Shel, 1991 (Box JGS 4, Folder 59)
- Dorgan, Thomas, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 60)
- Dorin, Paul, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 61)
- Dornfried, circa 1987 (Box JGS 4, Folder 62)
- Doru-Ghiocel, Olas, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 63)
- Dostal, Jaroslav, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 64)
- Douglas, Melvyn, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 65)
- Dremlyukh, Kirill, 1998 (Box JGS 4, Folder 66)
- Drewinski, Lex, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 67)
- Drobizky, Edvard, 1975-1976 (Box JGS 4, Folder 68)
- Drooker, Eric, 1988 (Box JGS 4, Folder 69)
- Druch, Ryszard, 1992-1995 (Box JGS 4, Folder 70)
- Drucker, Mort, 1986-1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 71)
- Drudginiy, Valentin, 1996 (Box JGS 4, Folder 72)
- Drummey, Jack, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 4, Folder 73)
- Druzhinin, Valentin, 1991-1995 (Box JGS 4, Folder 74)
- Drzewiecki, P., undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 75)
- Dubovsky, Alexandr, 1991-1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 76)
- Duffy, J.C., 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 77)
- Duhayon, Serge, 1991-1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 78)
- Duncan, Kevin, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 4, Folder 79)
- Duquette, Steven, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 80)
- Dzajkov, Spiro, 1996 (Box JGS 4, Folder 81)
- Dziegiel, W., circa 1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 82)
- Eastman, Kevin, 1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 83)
- Eaton, Tom, 1992 (Box JGS 4, Folder 84)
- Earl, Bill, 1994 (Box JGS 4, Folder 85)
- Ebrahiminejad, circa 1975 (Box JGS 4, Folder 86)
- Ebun, undated (Box JGS 4, Folder 87)
- Edua, Szucs, 1988-1993 (Box JGS 4, Folder 88)